<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>andys portfolio✌</title>
    <link>https://ahuynh.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on andys portfolio✌</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 14:33:41 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ahuynh.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sustainable Development Goals (SDG) Lesson</title>
      <link>https://ahuynh.io/posts/sdglesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 14:33:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ahuynh.io/posts/sdglesson/</guid>
      <description>SDG Lesson Slides Understanding Engineers Australia&amp;rsquo;s Code of Ethics
https://www.mentimeter.com/app/presentation/alpaomqq5gzywq3u56n2zjsi6ygc8osq
Lesson Plan 1. Lesson Starter/ Hook &amp;amp; Introduction Time: 2.5 min
Activity: For this part of the lesson, I will ask students to connect their devices (mobile/laptop) to Mentimeter which allows the lesson to be fully interactive with real-time feedback.
Purpose: The purpose of this lesson is to recognise how engineer&amp;rsquo;s promote sustainability through the Engineers Australia&amp;rsquo;s Code of Ethics. In addition, to apply Code 4 of EA&amp;rsquo;s Code of Ethics to existing or past projects and relate them to the Sustainability Development Goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://ahuynh.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 05:07:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ahuynh.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me - Andy Huynh Education Doctor of Philosophy in Mechanical Engineering (2021 - Current) University of Western Australia
Master of Professional Engineering in Mechanical Engineering (2019 - 2021) University of Western Australia
Bachelor of Science in Engineering Science and Accounting (2016 - 2018) University of Western Australia
Employment Academic Teaching (2021 - Current) University of Western Australia
Research Assistant (2020 - 2021) Intelligent Systems for Medicine Laboratory
Achievements William and Marlene Schrader Prize in Biomedical Engineering - Prize $2,000 Awarded to the student who achieved the highest mark in the field of biomedical engineering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflections on Learning and Teaching</title>
      <link>https://ahuynh.io/posts/reflectionsonlearningandteaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 03:54:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ahuynh.io/posts/reflectionsonlearningandteaching/</guid>
      <description>Lesson 1: Setting the Scene Lesson 2: Active Learning Strategies for Collaborative Small Group Teaching In engineering, I believe using both summative and formative assessments are appropriate. Both of these types of assessments allow me to assess student learning and give me opportunities to give and receive feedback. This is especially important as it allows both parties, the teacher and the student, to evaluate our work. It allows myself to assess the effectiveness of my teaching and the student to evaluate their learning and understanding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching Philosophy</title>
      <link>https://ahuynh.io/posts/teachingphilosophy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 03:44:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ahuynh.io/posts/teachingphilosophy/</guid>
      <description>Introduction “By learning you will teach; by teaching you will learn”
This is a quote that has resonated with me throughout my years as a student, and more recently as a teacher - it concisely summarises my teaching philosophy.
My teaching philosophy was first sparked from a short exchange with my Supervisor while I was preparing for my first class, &amp;lsquo;Mechanisms and Machines&amp;rsquo;, a farily difficult course. Seeing that I was stressing out revising the content I learned a few years back, he jokingly told me &amp;ldquo;You never really learn something until you have taught it&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
